(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-08-15T18:11:09.868400",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
いっせーのーせーで 踏み込むゴールライン
Altogether now, stepping onto the goal line
僕らは 何も 何も まだ知らぬ
We don't know anything, anything yet
一線越えて 振り返るともうない
Crossing the line, looking back, it's no longer there
僕らは 何も 何も まだ知らぬ
We don't know anything, anything yet
閃く 汗が こぼれるのさ
Glistening sweat is spilling out
覚えてない ことも たくさんあっただろう
There must have been plenty of things we don't remember
誰も 彼も シルエット
Everyone and everything is just a silhouette
大事にしてたもの 忘れたフリをしたんだよ
We pretended to forget the things we held dear
なんにもないよ 笑えるさ
There's nothing to it, we can laugh it off
いっせーのーせーで 思い出す少年
Altogether now, the boy remembers
僕らは 何もかもを 欲しがった
We wanted to have everything
わかってんの あぁ 気づいてんの
I know, ah, I've noticed
時計の針は 日々は止まらない
The hands of the clock, the days never stop
奪って 奪って 奪っていく
Taking, taking, taking it all away
流れる 時と 記憶
Flowing time and memories
遠く 遠く 遠くになって
Getting further, further, further away
覚えてない ことも たくさんあっただろう
There must have been plenty of things we don't remember
誰も 彼も シルエット
Everyone and everything is just a silhouette
恐れてやまないこと 知らないフリをしたんだよ
We pretended not to know what we feared without end
なんにもないよ 笑えるさ
There's nothing to it, we can laugh it off
ひらりとひらりと 舞っている
Fluttering and dancing
木の葉のように 憂うことなく
Like tree leaves, without sorrow
焦燥もなく 過ごしていたいよ
Or impatience, I want to spend time
覚えてない ことも たくさんあったけど
There were probably many things I didn't remember, but
きっとずっと変わらないものがあることを教えてくれた
You taught me that there are things that will never change
あなたは 消えぬ 消えぬ シルエット
You are a fading, fading silhouette
大事にしたいもの 持って 大人になるんだ
I'll grow up holding onto what I cherish
どんな時も 離さずに 守り続けよう
I will keep protecting it without letting go
そしたら いつかの日か 何にもかもを 笑えるさ
Then someday, we'll be able to laugh at everything
ひらりとひらりと 舞っている
Fluttering and dancing
木の葉が 飛んでいく
The leaves fly away
いっせーのーせで踏み込むゴールライン
In one go, stepping over the goal line...
僕らは何も何もまだ知らぬ
We still don't know anything at all.
一線越えて振り返るともうない
Crossing the line, looking back, it's already gone.
僕らは何も何もまだ知らぬ
We still don't know anything at all.
うだっちゅうだっちゅうだっちゅうく
Fired up, fired up, get fired up!
煌めく汗がこぼれるのさ
Sweat glistens and spills.
覚えてないこともたくさんあっただろう
There must have been many things we don't remember.
誰も彼もシルエット
Everyone, every silhouette...
大事にしてたもの、忘れたふりをしたんだよ
We pretended to forget the things we cherished.
なにもないよ、笑えるさ
There's nothing, we can laugh.
いっせーのーせで、思い出す少年
In one go, remembering the boy.
僕らは何もかもを欲しがった
We wanted everything.
わかってるって、あぁ気づいてるって
We know, ah, we realize.
時計の針は日々は止まらない
The clock's hands won't stop day by day.
奪って奪って奪ってく
Taking, taking, taking away...
流れる時と記憶
Flowing time and memories,
遠く遠く遠くになって
getting farther and farther away.
覚えてないこともたくさんあっただろう
There must have been many things we don't remember.
誰も彼もシルエット
Everyone, every silhouette.
恐れてやまないこと、知らないふりをしたんだよ
We pretended not to know what we feared.
なにもないよ、笑えるさ
There's nothing, we can laugh.
ひらりとひらりと舞っている
Fluttering and fluttering like the leaves,
木の葉の様に憂うことなく焦燥もなく過ごしていたいよ
I want to spend my days without worry or impatience.
覚えてないこともたくさんあったけど
There were many things we don't remember,
きっとずっと変わらないものがあることを
but surely there are things that will never change.
教えてくれたあなたは消えぬ消えぬシルエット
You, the silhouette that never fades, taught me.
大事にしたいもの持って大人になるんだ
I want to hold onto the things I cherish and become an adult.
どんな時も離さずに守り続けよう
I'll keep protecting without letting go, no matter when.
そしたらいつの日かに何もかもを笑えるさ
Then someday, we can laugh at everything.
ひらりとひらりと舞っている
Fluttering and fluttering...
木の葉が飛んでいく
The leaves are flying away.
Akhirnya 3D!
Finally, 3D!
Gimana?
How is it?
Wah, anime banget gak eh?
Is it very anime? Hey!
Heh, berisik kalian, ya!
Are you guys noisy?
Entar, aku taruh dulu ya. Uh!
Wait, I'll put this down first. Uh!
Berat.
Heavy.
Oke, kalau gitu, Kobo-Kobo, Kobo-Kobo, Kobo Kanaeru at your service.
Okay, if so... Kobo-Kobo, Kobo Kanaeru at your service.
Let me be your sun to shine your day. Hehe!
Oke, kita nge-vlog kali ya.
Okay, let's v-log, shall we?
Guys, welcome back to my channel!
Don't forget to like, sub, and komen, and give Kobo... give Kobo, eh... I mean, join Kobo's Nimbuzz! Let's go!
Don't forget to like, sub, and... uh, comment and give Kobo... give Kobo, eh... I mean, uh, join Kobo's Nimbuzz! Let's go!
Oke, di sini aku memperlihatkan nih pulau kecil aku ya.
Okay, here I want to show you my small island.
Hanya gubuk kecil doang.
It's just a small hut.
Di situ ada perahu ya, di situ ada perahu.
Over there, there's a boat, you see.
Soalnya, Kobo biasa pindah-pindah pulau ya.
Because Kobo usually moves from island to island.
Karena merchandise Kobo tu banyak, gak cuma di pulau ini doang.
Because Kobo's merchandise is a lot, not just on this island alone.
Nih lihat ya, tuh.
Look at that!
Tuh, tinggi banget tapi ya.
Tuh, it's very tall, right?
Ya tadi kalian di awal udah lihat ya, cuman...
Yeah, you guys saw it earlier, right?
emang apa ya, tinggi banget jadi rada capek ke sana. Jadi nanti aja ya Kobo tunjukin ke kalian ya.
It's very tall, so it's quite tiring to go there, so I'll show it to you guys later, okay?
Oke-oke.
Okay, okay.
Terus, outfit check!
Then, outfit check!
Outfit-nya di-check!
Oh, outfit check!
Oke, gitu. Shyu-shyu-shyu,
Okay, like this. Shoo-shoo-shoo!
look at my shoes!
Look at my shoes. Ooh, the details!
Ooh, the details! Ooh, kalian bisa lihat gak?
Ooh, the details! Ooh, can you guys see it?
Ha!
Hehe!
Terus ya, biasalah ya.
And then, usual, yeah?
Terus ini ada... jaket ya, gocap dapat juga di pasar malam.
And this has a jacket, you see, custom made at Pasar Malam.
Tinggal modif dikit, nih ada kasih nama brand Rangeoman, keren banget ya.
It's slightly modified, with the brand name "Rangeoman", it's so cool, right?
Jadi kayak mahal juga gitu loh.
So it looks expensive too, you see.
Keliatan mahal.
See? Looks expensive.
Terus ya, sepatunya thrifting aja lah ya.
Then the shoes are thrifted, you know?
Ya, ada yang minjam M-chan, ada nih...
Yeah, some are borrowed from M--chan, and this...
eh, sport bra juga punya minjam ya.
...sport bra is also borrowed, you know.
Ya, gitulah!
Yeah, like that!
Aku masih mau nunjukin... eh?
I still want to show... eh?
Eh, udah jam berapa kah ini?
Eh, what time is it already?
Eh? Aduh, sebentar-sebentar guys!
Eh? Aduh, wait-wait guys!
Aku harus ke sekolah dulu!
I have to go to school first!
Ah, iseng-iseng.
Ah, yikes, yikes!
Sorry, sorry, sorry!
Sebentar-sebentar. Aku harus ke sekolah dulu!
Wait, wait! I have to go to school first!
Ay! Cillia, tolong bantu!
Ay! Cillia, please help!
Cillia! Iya, Cillia, dalangin!
Cillia! Yeah, Cillia, drive it!
Ah, Moto, Ayako!
Moto, Ayako!
Aku takut!
I'm scared!
Aku gak mau telat!
I'm gonna be late!
Cepat-cepat, Moto, Ayako, gambar-gambar!
Ah, hurry-hurry, Moto, Ayako, come on, come on!
Ah, aku takut telat, cepetan semoga gak sempit!
Ah, I'm scared I'll be late, hurry up, hopefully I'm not late!
Akhirnya...
Finally...
nyampai kelas!
...homeroom class!
Ada Ayame.
There's Ayame!
Oh! Asmara
Kalian ada yang gak sih yang, relax?
Do you guys have anyone you like?
Yang rasanya jatuh cinta?
Who make you fall in love?
Rasanya tuh berbunga-bunga deh.
It feels like... blooming flowers!
Dag dig dug hatiku
My heart pounds
Saat aroma mu lewati hidungku
as your aroma tickles my nose,
Melotot mataku
my eyes widen
Melihatmu lewat di depanku
seeing you pass in front of me.
Seorang biasa saja
An ordinary person...
Apa pantas tuk bersanding denganmu?
do I deserve to stand by your side?
Overthinking, tapi gak mau ambil pusing
Overthinking, but don't want to stress
Karna aku bukan kaum mendang-mending
because I'm not one to hesitate.
Oh asmara, berdebar rasanya
Oh, romance, my heart flutters
'Ku di dekatmu
when I'm near you.
Oh asmara, dengar bisikan cinta lirih matamu
Oh, romance, hear your loving whispers,
Hantam jantungku, oh asmara
striking my heart, oh romance.
Hari ke-sekian, masih tak berhasil
The umpteenth day, still failing
mendekatimu
to get close to you.
Ugh bagaimanaaa... Melelehkan beku hatimu!
Ugh, how to melt your frozen heart?
"Mending nyerah dah?" Oh tentu tidak
"Better give up?" Oh, absolutely not!
Demi gapai impian, kita harus terus belajar
To reach our dreams, we must keep learning,
belajar memahami bahasa cintamu!
learning to understand your love language!
Oh asmara, berdebar rasanya
Oh, romance, my heart flutters
'Ku di dekatmu
when I'm near you.
Oh asmara, dengar bisikan cinta lirih matamu
Oh, romance, hear your loving whispers.
Oh asmara, balas sinyal citaku
Oh, romance, reply to my heart's signal
sekali saja!
just once!
Oh asmara, tidak adakah ruang dalam hatimu
Oh, romance, is there no room in your heart
tersisa untukku?
left for me?
Sore itu, tumben-tumbenan kau duluan yang datang menghampiriku
That afternoon, you surprisingly came to me first.
Oh asmara, berdebar rasanya
Oh, romance, my heart flutters
'Ku di dekatmu
when I'm near you.
Oh asmara, dengar bisikan cinta lirih matamu
Oh, romance, hear your loving whispers.
Oh asmara, berdebar rasanya 'ku di dekatmu
Oh, romance, my heart flutters when I'm near you.
Oh asmara, dengar bisikan cinta lirih matamu
Oh, romance, hear your loving whispers...
Oh asmara
Oh, romance!
Terjawab semua sudah teka-teki mu
All your riddles have been answered,
Karena kini ku telah menjadi milikmu
because now I have become yours.
Milikmu...
Yours...
Selamat 3D debut!
Happy 3D debut!
Eh bentar, itu kenapa ada papan...
Wait, what is that?
Ini lagi ngapain nih?
What are you doing?
Ini kenalin... Pacar baru!
Introducing my new boyfriend!
Namanya siapa ini?
What's his name?
Enggak sih, enggak tau, tapi ganteng kan?
I don't know, but he's handsome, right?
Mohon maaf nih, bukan gimana-gimana nih
Wait, sorry, I'm not judging or anything,
Tapi biasa nih cowok yang kayak gini nih...
but usually guys like this...
Halo, cowok yang kayak gini biasanya ada maunya.
Hello, guys like this usually have motives.
Apa tuh maunya?
What motive?
Enggak enggak, jangan dengerin dia. Ayang, jangan dengerin dia!
No, no, don't listen to her! Hey, don't listen to her!
Enggak, enggak mungkin. Ayang, kamu dengerin aku nggak sih?
No, he wouldn't! Ayang, listen to me!
Ayang!
Ayang, hey!
Mending dengerin aku dulu nih.
You guys better listen to me first!
Nggak bisa kayak gini ya,, wah.
You can't be like that, y'know.
Makanya, mendingan kamu tuh jadi gepeng biar sama nih!
That's why you should be short too, so it matches!
Susah-susah nunggu dewa 3D...
Such a hassle, waiting for 3D!
Udah-udah, gak usah ribut!
Enough, enough, don't make a fuss!
Masa kardus gini doang diributin!
Making a fuss over a piece of cardboard!
Bukan kardus!
It's not cardboard!
Udah ya, udah ya... Mohon maaf nih.
Alright, alright... I'm so sorry.
Demi kebaikan kamu, mendingan kamu fokus...
For your own good, you better focus...
Ini ku bawa dulu ya. Emang boleh?!
I'll take this first. Is that allowed?!
Boleh!
Allowed!
Semangat 3D!
Keep up the 3D spirit!
Jangan pacar aku...
No, don't take my boyfriend...
君の心に包まれたまま 愛を誓い…
Vows of love that we made, in your heart they will stay,
眠れない夜 何度過ぎてもね 受け止めて
No matter how many sleepless nights pass, please accept it.
今すぐ逢いたい 涙止まらない
I want to see you right now, tears won't stop,
触れたくて 好きだから 苦しくて
I want to touch you, because loving you hurts so much.
君のこと思うほど
The more I think about you,
この涙こぼれるの
the more these tears overflow.
このまま逢えないとしても 誰より好きだから…
Even if we can't meet like this, because I love you most...
Bye Bye さっきしたばかりなのに
Bye-bye, even though we just did it moments ago,
「逢いたい」がまたあふれるの
“I want to see you” overflows once again.
消えてしまいそうあの日の One Kiss
That fading kiss from that day...
君からのメールを待つのか
waiting for your email.
君と会えば迫る タイムリミット 二人の時間 大事に
When we meet, the time limit approaches. Let's cherish our time.
ババイして また会いたい 君とのメールで また再会
Saying bye-bye, wanting to meet again, reunited through emails.
帰る景色 街は Twilight いっそのこと 君を奪い去りたい
Scenery on the way back, the city at twilight. I'd rather snatch you away.
君のぬくもり消える頃 夢から覚めれば現実の Door
When your warmth fades, waking from the dream to reality's door.
君のこと思うほど この涙こぼれるの このまま逢えないとしても 誰より好きだから…
The more I think about you, tears overflow. Even if we can't meet, because I love you...
I LUV YOU LUV YOU 夜が明ければ
I LUV YOU LUV YOU When the night clears up
探す君だけ 目を閉じれば My LUV for You...
Searching only for you, close your eyes, My LUV for You...
あなたと… 今すぐ逢いたい 限りある TIME
With you... I want to see you right now, in this limited time.
“永遠の愛” 信じてはみたい 離れること考えると 胸が真二つに裂けるよ
Wanting to believe in "eternal love". Thinking of parting tears my heart in two.
可愛い顔で 夜が明ければ引き裂かれる
With your cute face, when dawn breaks, we're torn apart.
カウントダウンのように Break Love baby love baby 言葉は freeze
Breaking like a countdown. Love baby love baby, words freeze.
今日が始まった またね see you… 思えば思うほど
Today begins, see you again... The more I think about you,
降り積もる “想い” 会えば会うほど 側でいたいと強く願うほど
the feelings pile up. The more we meet, the more I wish to stay close.
明日さえ見えなくて “永遠” いつか見つけるまで 話したくはない 離れたくはない
Not even seeing tomorrow, until I find "eternity", I don't want to talk, I don't want to part.
Love you baby love for you 君を離さない
Love you baby love for you, I won't let you go.
君のこと思うほど この涙こぼれるの
The more I think about you, the more these tears overflow.
あけない夜の中 ひとり 君しか見えなくて…
Alone in the endless night, you're all I can see...
君の心に包まれたまま 愛を誓い…
Vows of love that we made, in your heart they will stay...
眠れない夜 何度過ぎてもね 受け止めて
No matter how many sleepless nights pass, please accept it.
今すぐ逢いたい 涙止まらない 触れたくて 好きだから 苦しくて
I want to see you right now, tears won't stop, because loving you hurts so much.
I LUV YOU (LUV YOU) LUV YOU (LUV YOU)... 夜が明ければ
I LUV YOU LUV YOU... When the night clears up
探す君だけ 目を閉じれば My LUV for You...
Searching only for you, close your eyes, My LUV for You...
あなたと… 今すぐ逢いたい 限りある TIME
With you... I want to see you right now, in this limited time.
“永遠の愛” 信じてはみたい 離れること考えると 胸が真二つに裂けるよ
Wanting to believe in "eternal love". Thinking of parting tears my heart in two.
可愛い顔で 夜が明ければ引き裂かれる
With your cute face, when dawn breaks, we're torn apart.
カウントダウンのように Break Love baby love baby 言葉は freeze
Breaking like a countdown. Love baby love baby, words freeze.
今日が始まった またね see you…
Today begins, see you again...
君の心に包まれたまま 愛を誓い…
Vows of love that we made, in your heart they will stay...
眠れない夜 何度過ぎてもね 受け止めて
No matter how many sleepless nights pass, please accept it.
今すぐ逢いたい 涙止まらない 触れたくて 好きだから 苦しくて
I want to see you right now, tears won't stop, because loving you hurts so much.
I LUV YOU LUV YOU... My LUV for You... あなたと…
I LUV YOU LUV YOU... My LUV for You... With you...
Ooh...
Yeah, yeah.
Ah, so sun...
Sun?
What's going on? Why are you crying?
Why are you so sad? We just sang a great song together, come on!
Your heart hurts? But why?
My boyfriend cheated on me!
He goes for Zeta!
Wait... Wait... Hold on a moment.
You have a... You have a boyfriend?
Tell me who he is, tell me where he is, and I will take care of...
Everything, Dad will take care of everything for you, Kobo.
I don't know, I don't even know his name, but I love him.
Um, a what?
Um, I don't really think I understand, but it's okay.
It's okay, son. Look.
Sometimes...
Things in life just... they just don't go your way, but it's all right. You'll be okay, I promise.
No!
No, no!
I can't... I can't take this anymore!
Here.
Kids, man.
Here! Just shoot me!
A gun? Kobo, I can't! I can't do that!
I can't do that, you're my son!
Tem-bak, tem-bak! Ako ngatan!
All right, all right. Well, it is my job after all, so I guess I'll do it.
Now, if you insist, Kobo, take a place where you want to perish.
I think I will... maybe, maybe here.
All right. Stand really still. Say your prayers.
Shoot me, dad! Shoot me, dad!
Rest in peace.
Ah! Ah!
Doing my job.
What? What happened here?
Kiara, what did you do?
Kiara! Oh, I mean, I... I didn't do...
Anything. All right, look. All right, hold on. I know what it looks like.
Look, I shot... I shot her with a water gun, all right? With a water gun.
Look, it's not lethal or anything.
Did you just dead?
She just playing dead.
She's playing... You should be teaching her... She's playing and stuff like this.
You know kids, Kiara look.
That only leads one.
She's faking.
Kobo!
Ah...
One of her failure's parents, I wonder.
Come on. Live.
Come back to me! Come on!
Mami?
Yes, yes, yes.
Sorry, mami.
It's okay. It's okay.
Oh, Kobo, it took you long enough. Come on! Get up before daddy gets in trouble!
Oh my god.
I'm back with the father!
Well, thank god.
What happened, Kobo? What happened?
My boyfriend cheated on me.
Who's your boyfriend? Where is he?
That's what I said.
I don't know his name, but I love him.
Listen here, you little shit. Forget about him. Mami is here.
Let's just have fun together, okay?
Have fun.
Let's go!
Yeah, let's go. Sounds like fun, you guys.
I'm... I'm coming too, right?
I'm invited? Right?
Can you go buy milk?
Really? Really?
Really? For breakfast? Milk?
Yeah. Again? We need it.
Yeah. Bye-bye!
Whatever.
Kobo, come on. Let's do something fun, okay?
Mami, and don't die!
Okay!
ロマンスの不祥事 逃がさない
Romance scandals won't get away.
消してあげる
I'll make it disappear.
マミ!
Mami!
Aku mau jadi presiden!
は? ナンパイン?
Huh? Nampanin?
Yar, aku nggak di-PHP cowok lagi.
No, you're still a baby. Let me be the president instead.
は? 先生!
Huh? Sensei!
私が大統領になったら 人の男にちょっかいかける女は島流しにします
If I become the president, any woman who flirts with other men will be exiled to an island!
先生!
Sensei!
私が大統領になったら いや、ただの友達だよ~って誤魔化す奴は 秘蔵から電気を流します
If I become the president, It's just my friend, you know! Anyone who makes that excuse, I'll electrify them from the outlet!
だ・だ・だ・大胆不敵 センセーショナルクローズアップ
D, d, d, don't cry, sensational close-up!
D,D,D,Don't cry やるぜ徹底的にリサーチだ
D, d, d, don't cry, I'll do it thoroughly.
大嫌い? しょうがない? クズは病気ね バイバイ・バイバイ
Hate it? So what? Scum is a disease. Bye-bye, bye-bye.
権力! 財産! 地位名声!!
Power! Property! Status, prestige!
なにもないけど裁きたいでしょ?
You want to judge me for nothing, don't you?
だ・だ・だ・大統領になったらね まずは君を捕まえるね
When I'm president, I'll get you first.
濡れたタオルで 洗いさらそう吐かせるね
With a wet towel, I'll make you tell me everything.
誰ですか あの女 どーゆーんですか そうですか
Who is that woman? Are you seeing her? Is that so?
ロマンスの不祥事 逃がさない
Romance scandals won't get away.
消してあげる シル・ヴ・プレ・プレ・プレジデント
I'll make it disappear. Shiru-vu-pure-pure-president!
先生!
Sensei!
ロマンスの不祥事 逃がさない 消してあげる
I won't let the romance scandal get away. I'll make it disappear.
宣誓！ 私が大統領になったら
Oath! When I'm president...
人の男にちょっかいかける女は島流しにします
Any woman who messes with another's man gets exiled!
宣誓！ 私が大統領になったら
Oath! When I'm president...
いやただの友達だよって誤魔化す奴は、ヘソから電流を流します
I'll shock anyone who claims "we're just friends"!
だ・だ・だ・だ 大胆不敵 センセーショナル クローズアップ
D-d-d-d-daredevil, sensational close-up!
d,d,d,don't cry やるぜ 徹底的に リサーチだ
D-d-d-don't cry, I'll thoroughly research this!
大嫌い？ しょうがない？ クズは病気ね バイバイ・バイ
Hate it? Can't be helped? Scum is a disease, bye-bye.
権力！ 財産！ 位階 名声！！
Power! Property! Status, prestige!
なににも ない けど 裁き たい でしょ？
You want to judge me for nothing, don't you?
だ・だ・だ・だ 大統領 に なったら ね まずは君を捕まえるね
When I'm president... First, I'll catch you.
濡れたタオルで 洗いざらい吐かせ得るね
With a wet towel, I'll make you confess everything!
誰ですか あの女 （いやぁ〜）
Who is that woman? (Oh, my...)
ダメですか そうですか （あちぁ〜）
Is that no good? Is that how it is? (Oops...)
ロマンスの不祥事 逃がさない 消してあげる
I won't let the romance scandal get away, I'll erase it.
し・る・ぷれぷれ プレジデント
S'il vous, s'il vous, President!
宣誓！ 私 が 大統領 に なったら
Oath! When I'm president...
ただの仕事の付き合いだよ？って言う奴は二度と働けなくしてやります
Anyone who says "it's just a business relationship" will never work again!
宣誓！ 以下略！
Oath! The rest is abbreviated!
いや向こうが強引でさーっていう男の口にはレジンを流し込んで固めてやります！
If a guy says "she was too pushy," I'll pour resin in his mouth and harden it!
み・み・み・み 密着 まるでドン・ファン 気取り スキャン ダラス
Close, close, close, close! Like Don Juan, scandalous!
ま・ま・ま・ま 末端価格 甲斐性 なしのスクープね
Worthless scoop with no reliability!
愛はない？ 理由じゃない 悪くないのね はいはいはい
No love? That's not the reason, not bad, right? Yes, yes, yes.
軽薄！ のうのう！ いけしゃあしゃあ！！
Frivolous! Shameless! Unbelievable!
なにもない とか ありえない でしょ？
You can't just say there's nothing, right?
だ・だ・だ・だ 大統領 に なっても ね たぶん君は変わらないね
Even if I'm president... You probably won't change.
しらっとぼけて のらりくらりかわすのね（で・で・で！）
You'll just play dumb and dodge it (Right, right, right!)
デート ですか こんばんは （うわぁ〜）
Is this a date? Good evening (Whoa~)
本気 ですか そうですか （ほらんっ〜）
Are you serious? Is that so? (Look here~)
情熱 とは 不注意 微熱 も 消してしまいたい
Passion is carelessness, I want to extinguish even a slight fever.
だ・だ・だ・だ 大統領 に なったら ね マジで君を捕まえるね
When I'm president... I'll catch you for real.
濡れたタオルで 洗いざらい吐かせ得るね （ど・ど・ど！）
With a wet towel, I'll make you confess everything! (D-d-d!)
どこ ですか 今 あなた （おゃぁ〜？）
Where are you right now? (Oh my~?)
見っけちゃった バレちゃった （おらぁ〜！）
I found you, you've been caught! (Take this!)
Thank you!
Yay!
I'm good now, thank you!
Mommy has to go home and rest, but I will sleep and dream about you!
Let's go!
So, gambatte, Kobo-chan.
So, do your best, Kobo-chan.
Aku cinta kamu! Bye-bye!
I love you! Bye-bye!
I'm not going home yet, okay? I still want to show you guys something.
Aku mau tunjukin sesuatu yang keren banget.
I want to show you something really cool.
A trick using my Shaman power... Look at this!
Udan, torgira! Keren banget ya!
Rain and thunder! It's so cool!
LeNsya-ma no chikara da!
It's LeNsya-ma's power!
This is also the first time you guys see my jellyfish umbrella, right?
Look at it, it's cute, right? Cute, right? Cute, right?
By the way, every time you send a super chat, it will give more power to the rain.
Setiap kalian kirim super chat, akan menambah kekuatan hujan.
Every time you send a super chat, it will add power to the rain.
Thank you for the super chat! Lumayan bentar, kayaknya aku belum... belum mandi juga.
Thank you for the super chat! I haven't taken a bath yet either.
Nice! Thank you! Kore wa kimi-tachi no ai da! Arigatou!
Nice! Thank you! This is your love! Thank you!
Yaa, thank you! Thank you, tapi aku nggak bisa berenang!
Yeah, thank you! Thank you, but I can't swim!
Eh, sebentar sebentar, aku nggak bisa berenang! Putar... Aduh...
Wait, wait, I can't swim! Spin... Oh gosh...
うっ...
Ugh...
ヤゴーさん、助けて！
Yagoo, help me!
できる！できるぶわ...
I can do it! I can do...
Dekiru buwa is love!
できる！
I can do it!
Ice! Oke, thank you!
Ice! Okay, thank you!
My back hurts.
Akhirnya pulang juga ke rumah...
Finally came back home...
...untuk pakai jas hujan.
...to wear a raincoat.
Luckily, my outfit is waterproof.
Oh, by the way, welcome! Welcome to my lighthouse, yōkoso!
Oh, by the way, welcome! Welcome to my lighthouse, welcome!
Ini dalamnya merch store aku.
This is inside my merch store.
Aku room tour dikit kali ya. Oke, let's go do a quick room tour, oke?
I'll do a quick room tour. Okay, let's go do a quick room tour, oke?
Jadi di sini ada tangga karena merch store aku tuh tinggi banget sebenarnya, cuman ya...
So here there are stairs because my merch store is actually really high, but well...
ya udahlah ya di ini aja lah ya di lantai ini aja.
...whatever, let's just do it on this floor.
Nanti kita ke atas nanti-nanti aja, oke? Oke.
We'll go upstairs later, okay? Okay.
Lalu, biasanya habis pulang sekolah aku langsung tidur.
Then, usually after coming home from school I immediately sleep.
Tapi ya karena aku buat tamu di sini, jadi ya udah...
But since I have a guest here, well...
...aku room tour aja deh, ya kan ya? Ya kan? Oh, ini namanya Oyamatadase.
...I'll just do a room tour, right? Right? Oh, this is called Oyamatadase.
Iya kan? Lucu lucu lucu lucu.
Right? Cute, cute, cute, cute.
Oke, lanjut.
Okay, next.
Eh, di sini biasa tempat lutingan-lutingan, makanan-makanan diambil.
Uh, here is usually where loot and food are taken.
Terus ini kalau mau nyantai ya sama teman-teman yang biasa saya luting.
And here if you want to chill with friends I usually loot with.
Nah, ada apa lagi ya? Ada boneka-boneka.
Well, what else is there? There are dolls.
Ini banyak boneka, sori ya.
There are lots of dolls, sorry.
Terus ada, ini ada ada Fajri, Kiply, Kupli, absen dulu yuk.
And there's Fajri, Kiply, Kupli, let's roll call first.
Ya, Rio ada Rayi, ada Ryu.
There's Rio, Rayi, Ryu.
Ya, banyak banget ya, guys. Terus ada beberapa koleksi instrumen aku.
Yeah, there are so many, guys. And there are some of my instrument collections.
Kayak salah satunya piano, keyboard sih, keyboard.
Like a piano, keyboard, yeah, keyboard.
Sama terus ada tempat aku biasa streaming di sini.
And then, there's where I usually stream here.
Apa sih? Ada monitor tadinya, cuman...
What is it? There was a monitor earlier, but...
Aku lagi pakai TV ya, lagi nyantai dulu. Terus tuh i lihat ada ukulele, hihi.
I'm using the TV, just relaxing first. And then I see there's a ukulele, heh!
Sama terus ada kulkas.
And then there's a fridge.
Sama ini, ada dua instrumen yang sering aku mainin.
And this, there are two instruments I frequently play.
Yaitu gitar listrik sama gitar akustik. Nah, sih, aku lebih sering main gitar akustik.
That is, an electric guitar and an acoustic guitar. I more often play the acoustic guitar.
Nah yang tadi aku mainin tuh yang ini, guys, yang gitar listrik. Jere-de-ding! Jere-de-de-ding!
Now, the one I just played is this one, guys, the electric guitar. Jere-de-ding!
Ya, terus sama ada violin, ini jarang... lagi jarang sih, ya.
And there's a violin, this is rarely used, yeah.
Soalnya ini, ada tanaman ini.
Because of this, there's this plant.
Hmm, kantong semar udah, udah berkembang biak banyak banget. Hmm, ini nyoi.
Hmm, pitcher plants have already bred a lot. Hmm, this is nice.
Ya, kalian lihatlah apa lagi itu, tuh, langit-langit! Ah, ah, ah, langit-langit!
Yeah, you guys look at what else that is, look, the ceiling! The ceiling!
Aku punya lampu-lampu lucu di atas! Wah!
I have cute lights above! Wow!
Lucu ya, lampu-lampunya.
Cute, right, the lights.
Terus emang kayak apa sih, ceiling-nya lucu banget, kan? Gimana, gimana, gimana cantiknya kamar aku, kayak pemiliknya, iya enggak sih?
And the ceiling is so cute, right? How pretty is my room, like its owner, right?
Iya, iya. Aku tadi lihat, 'Kak Kobo, coba dong mainin instrumennya.'
Yeah, yeah. I just saw, "Kobo-chan, try playing the instrument."
Hah, mau gimana lagi ya? Biar aku baik hati dan tidak sombong,
Well, what can I do? To make sure I'm kind and not arrogant,
untung aku enggak berisik. Enggak ya, aku baik, aku lagi baik nih. Ya udah deh.
good thing I'm not noisy. No, I'm good, I'm being good right now. Oh well.
Kalian dengar sini, oke? Catat mati, kudo-sai, ne?
You guys listen here, okay? Take note, okay?
Aku mau ambil itu, gitar. Ya udah, aku main gitarnya aja deh.
I want to get that guitar. Oh well, I'll just play the guitar.
Sama buka jaket sebentar ya, oke? Tunggu di sini, sebentar.
And open my jacket for a moment, okay? Wait here.
Nih aku taruh dulu request, wujud-wujud, mau gitar, mau gitar nih.
Let me put the request first, wanting a guitar, wanting a guitar.
Lagu yang melow-melow, ya? Oke.
A mellow song, huh? Okay.
Lagu apa tuh kira-kira, Kobo? Ya kalian pasti tahu. Nyanyi bareng ya, yang tahu lagunya. Kita nge-galau bersama, oke?
What song could that be? Yeah, you guys definitely know. Sing along, those who know the song. Let's be emo together, okay?
薄紅の時を彩る花びら
Faint crimson-painted petals of time
ひらひら舞う光の中 僕らは笑えたはず
fluttering within the light, we should have been able to smile
鮮やかな日々に 僕らが残した
The vivid days that we left behind
砂の城は波に溶けて きっと夢が終わる
The sandcastle melts into the waves, surely the dream will end
真っ白な世界で目を覚ませば
If I wake up in a pure white world,
伸ばす腕は何方も掴まない
the arm I reach out grasps nothing.
薄紅の
Faint crimson
時を彩る花びら
petals coloring the passage of time
ぱらぱら舞う光の中僕は笑えたはず
fluttering in the dancing light, I should have smiled
鮮やかな日々に僕らが残した
The vibrant days we left behind
砂の城は波に溶けてきっと夢が終わる
The sandcastle melts into the waves, surely ending the dream
真っ白な世界で目覚めれば
Waking up in a pure white world,
伸す腕は何もつかめない
the arms I stretch out can't grasp anything.
見上げた空が近くなるほどに
As the sky I look up to gets closer,
僕は何を失った?
what did I lose?
透通る波映る僕らの影は蒼く遠く
The clear waves reflect our shadows, blue and far away.
あの日僕は世界を知りそれは光となった
That day I came to know the world, and it became light.
僕は歌うよ笑顔をくれた君が泣いているとき
I will sing when you, who gave me a smile, are crying,
ほんの少しだけでもいい君の支えになりたい
even if just a little, I want to be your support.
僕が泣いてしまった日に君がそうだったように
Just as you were on the day I cried.
僕がここに忘れたもの全て君がくれた宝もの
Everything I forgot here are treasures given by you;
形のないものだけが時の中で色褪せないまま
only things without form remain unfaded through time.
透通る波何度消してしまっても砂の城を僕は君と残そう
No matter how many times clear waves erase them, I will leave the sandcastle with you.
そこに光を集め僕は歌うよ笑顔をくれた君が泣いているとき
Gathering light there, I will sing when you, who gave me a smile, are crying.
頼りのない僕だけれど君のことを守りたい
Though I am unreliable, I want to protect you.
遠く離れた君のもとへこの光が空を越えて羽ばたいていく
To you far away, this light flies across the sky,
そんな歌を届けたい僕が贈るものは全て形のないものだけど
wanting to deliver such a song—everything I gift has no form, but
君の心の片隅で輝く星になりたい
I want to become a shining star in the corner of your heart.
遠く離れた君のもとへこの光が空を越えて羽ばたいていく
To you far away, this light flies across the sky,
そんな歌を届けたい僕が贈るものは全て形のないものだけど
wanting to deliver such a song—everything I gift has no form, but
君の心の片隅で輝く星になりたい
I want to become a shining star in the corner of your heart.
ちょっと怖かったなあ
That was a bit scary, haha.
はあ、少しさ、
Whew... a little bit,
ごめん、ごめん、
sorry, sorry,
I made some mistake 'cause I'm so nervous,
I made some mistakes 'cause I'm so nervous.
this is my first time in 3D life singing, singing with acoustic guitar.
This is my first time singing in 3D live with an acoustic guitar.
The pressure is different from from the usual karaoke.
The pressure is different from usual karaoke.
You know, you know? Sorry, sorry, grogy!
You know, you know? Sorry, sorry, feeling dizzy!
えへへ、
Ehehe...
まあ、ぎった、
Well...
いや、うだらはもういっか、もういいか、
Yeah, whatever, let's keep going.
よし、
Alright,
ちょっと待ってね、私タロ、これど、待ってね、私なろ、椅子から取って
wait, let me put this away first, let me move the chair...
Sudah ya guys ya, mari senang-senang bersamaku.
Alright guys, let's have fun together.
Ya, jadi tadi aku sudah menunjukkan bagaimana ruanganku dan isi-isinya.
Yeah, so earlier I showed what my room and its contents look like.
Tapi, masih ada satu... This one more thing you guys don't know, and I want to show you guys now.
But there's still one... This one more thing you guys don't know, and I want to show you guys now.
Now, right here. Yes, masih ada satu yang belum kalian tahu.
Now, right here. Yes, there's still one you guys don't know.
Eh kok, woi, rusak kah? Woi, woi, woi!
Eh huh, hey, is it broken? Hey, hey, hey!
Tada! Leave my private lift di Parisor Kobo.
Tada! Leave my private lift in Parisor Kobo.
Oke, sebentar-sebentar, aku punya sesuatu yang harus dipakai.
Okay, wait a minute, I have something I need to wear.
Tada! Now I'm ready, let's go to the sky!
Wah, gimana? Keren kan fitur baru merchandise baru aku?
Wah, how is it? Isn't the new feature of my new merch cool?
Iya, wah, seru banget.
Yeah, wow, so exciting.
Eh, kameramen, sini deh kameramen. Nih, lihat nih. Tinggi banget! So high!
Eh, cameraman, come here cameraman. Look at this. So high!
Ah, sedikit takut, takut nah. Kameramennya terbang guys, keren banget, padahal plafonnya kecil banget.
Ah, a bit scared. The cameraman is flying guys, so cool, even though the ceiling is super small.
Ah, ya udah kita harus nyebrang dulu ke sana ya. Soalnya, ya taulah, ya nanti kalian taulah mau ngapainlah.
Ah, oh well, we have to cross over there first. Because, you know, you'll know what we're gonna do later.
Cuman ini, aku enggak tahu pelanginya bisa diinjak apa enggak ya. Kayak, aku takut tembus. Jatuh kan enggak lucu ya, guys.
Only this, I don't know if the rainbow can be stepped on or not. Like, I'm afraid of falling through. Falling wouldn't be funny, guys.
Jadi, kita lompat aja, oke? I will jump, long jump, oke? Oke.
So, we'll just jump, okay? I will jump, long jump, oke? Oke.
Satu, dua, tiga, eh.
One, two, three, eh.
Scam! Kerenan aku, scam! Wiii!
Scam! I'm cooler, scam! Wheee!
Oke, oke. For real, this one for real, oke? Kali ini beneran. Satu, dua...
Okay, okay. For real, this one for real, okay? This time for real. One, two...
Tiga, wah!
Three, wah!
Gila, keren banget gua. Let's go!
Crazy, I'm so cool. Let's go!
Tada! Duh, kemon stage, kawaii desho?
Tada! Come on stage, isn't it cute?
Mite-mite, ada pelangi, lucu banget! Ada tiga, satu, dua, tiga. Terus ada awannya lagi mendung, lagi hujan, tapi ya...
Look, look, there's a rainbow, so cute! There are three, one, two, three. Then the clouds are cloudy, raining, but yeah...
Nanti bisa berubah lagi ya, kan aku pawang hujan, ya. Gampang lah ya masalah ini cuaca. Terus ada balon-balon, ada bintang, kirakira...
Later it can change again, right, I'm a rain shaman, yeah. It's easy, right, this weather issue. Then there are balloons, stars, sparkling...
Iih, lucu banget ada lantai, ada burung. Lihat enggak kalian?
Eek, so cute, there's a floor, there are birds. Did you see them?
Ne, minna, ja, kondo wa, Kobo chuu, idol ma?
Hey everyone, now, next, Kobo, an idol?
Hey. It's me! 準備はいいかい?
Hey. It's me! Are you ready?
もっと熱く高く
Higher and hotter,
光よりもはやく
faster than light
Your heart 連れてくよ Higher
Your heart, taking you higher
圧倒的に stunning 感じるはず Cuz why not?
Absolutely stunning, you should feel it, cuz why not?
ドキドキをあげる
Giving you heartthrobs,
Come on! It's show time!
それっぽいだけじゃねえ
Not just looking the part,
物足りないでしょ So
it's not enough, so
ようこそ私のア天地
Welcome to my domain
Anyone can keep up with me?
Anyone?
孤城から見渡す景色
The scenery overlooking from the castle
知ってるの私だけね!
I'm the only one who knows!
我就是那么完美
I am just that perfect
もっとAddictedに intoxicatedに
More addicted, intoxicated
全部射抜いてあげる Oh I'm too good!
Shooting right through you, oh I'm too good!
怖いものなんてない お遊びはオシマイ
Nothing to fear, playtime is over
ここから全てが始まってくよ
Everything starts from right here
Top of the top! Top of the world!
Top of the top!
这地球就是绕着我转
This earth revolves around me
Top of the top! Top of the world!
Top of the top! 怎样 不错吧 Huh?
Top of the top! How's that, pretty good huh?
高ぶる思い It's burning
Thumping feelings, it's burning
感じるはず Eye to eye
you'll feel it eye to eye
ドキドキがとまらない?
Heartthrobs won't stop?
Don't miss the best time!
私じゃなくちゃだね
It has to be me,
物足りないってほど
to the point of not being enough
最高的しか欲しくない
Only the best will do,
思いのまま 私ならね!
just as I want!
もっとmajesticに Enthusiasticに
More majestic, enthusiastic
視線奪ってあげる Oh I'm too bad!!
Stealing your gaze, oh I'm too bad!!
躊躇わずに抱きしめて
Embrace me without hesitation
高ぶる思い It's burning
Thumping feelings, it's burning
感じるはず Eye to eye
you'll feel it eye to eye
ドキドキがとまらない
Heartthrobs won't stop
私じゃなくちゃあね 物足りないってほど
Unless it's me, it's just not enough.
我来吸引这世界
I'll attract this world.
I'm the one who you've been waiting for
最棒にしかな欲しくない
I only want the absolute best.
思いのまま 私ならね！
Just as I want, because it's me!
谁 让我 那么 完美
Who else could make me so perfect?
もっとMajesticに Enthusiasticに
More majestic, more enthusiastic,
視線奪ってあげる Ooh, I'm too bad!!
I'll steal your gaze. Ooh, I'm too bad!!
踊ることなんてない 綻びは見せない
There's no stumbling, no showing flaws.
ここから世界は 広がっていくよ 明日へ
From here, the world expands toward tomorrow.
胸に手を当ててみたなら探して
If you place your hand on your chest, search for
本当の心と 絶えず突き上げる 振動が
your true heart, and the constant surging vibration
告げる真実を
that announces the truth.
ほら バイアスや 思い込みが
Look, even if biases and preconceptions
邪魔をしても 目を閉じないで
try to get in the way, don't close your eyes.
私は逃げない！ 最高を見せたい 貫くよ
I won't run away! I want to show you the best, and pierce through!
もっと熱く届く 光よりも速く Your heart連れて そう どこまでもHigher
Hotter and faster than light, taking your heart ever higher.
踊ることなんてない 綻びは見せない
There's no stumbling, no showing flaws.
ここから歴史は 刻まれてくから
From here, history is being carved out.
Just follow me! もっとAddictedに Intoxicatedに 全部射抜いてあげる Ooh, I'm too good!!
Just follow me! More addicted, more intoxicated, I'll pierce right through you. Ooh, I'm too good!!
怖いものなんてない お遊びはオシマイ
There's nothing to fear, playtime is over.
ここから全てが 始まってくよ
From here, everything begins.
Top of the top! Top of the world!
这地球就是绕着我转
This earth just spins around me.
Top of the top! Top of the world!
どうでもいいような 夜だけど
It's an unexceptional, ordinary night,
どよめき 煌めきと君も
with the noise, the sparkle, and you.
まだ止まった 刻む針も 入り浸った 散らかる部屋も
The clock hands are still frozen, the frequented, cluttered room too.
変わらないね 思い出しては 二人 歳を重ねてた
Nothing changed, as I remember, we both grew older together.
まだ止まった 落とす針を よく流した 聞き飽きるほど
The needle drops again, we've replayed it until we almost grew tired of it.
変わらないね 変わらないで いられたのは 君だけが
Nothing changed, please don't change, you were the only one who stayed.
無駄話で はぐらかして 触れた 先をためらうように
Deflecting with small talk, as if hesitating to touch.
足踏みして ずれた針を よそに 揃い始めた 息が
Treading carefully, our breaths began to sync aside the misplaced hands.
どうでもいいような 夜だけど
It's an unexceptional, ordinary night,
どよめき 煌めきと君も 踊ろう
dance with the noise, the sparkle, and you.
どうでもいいような 夜だけど
It's an average, boring night,
二人 刻もう
let's mark the time together.
透き通った 白い 肌 も
Your translucent, pale skin,
その 笑った 無邪気な 顔 も
and that carefree, smiling face.
変わらないね 変わらないで
Nothing changed, please don't change,
いられるのは 今 だけ が
this can only be right now.
見つめる ほど に 溢れる メモリー
The more I stare, the more memories overflow.
浮浮かす 心 に コーヒー を
A cup of coffee for a wavering heart,
乱れた部屋に 掠(かす)れたメロディー 混ざり合ってよう もう一度
a disheveled room, a scratchy melody, let's blend together once more.
どうでもいいような 夜だけど
It's an unexceptional, ordinary night,
どよめき 煌めきと君も 踊ろう
dance with my beating heart, my elation, and you.
どうでもいいような 夜だけど 二人
It's an average, boring night, the two of us...
どうでもいいような 夜だけど
It's an unexceptional, ordinary night
どよめき 煌めきと君も
The noise, the sparkle, and you
まだ 止まった 刻む 針 も
The clock hands are frozen again
入り浸った 散らかる 部屋 も
The frequented, cluttered room
変わらないね 思い出しては
Nothing changed, but as I look back
どうでもいいような 夜だけど
It's an unexceptional, ordinary night
どよめき 煌めきと君も踊ろう
Dance with the noise, the sparkle, and you
どうでもいいような 夜だけど
It's an unexceptional, ordinary night
二人刻もう ああ愛してと
Let's tick together... Oh, love me
どうでもいいから 僕だけを
Who cares, just look at me alone
ふらつき よろめきながらも
As we sway and stumble along
どうでもいいような 夜だけど
It's an unexceptional, ordinary night
ああ 二人刻もう
Ah, let's tick together
はぁ...
Haa...
どうだった？
How was it?
カレンが？
Was it cool?
せっ...くんかっこよかったっけ？
Wait, was I cool?
はぁ...
Sigh...
でも、みんな知ってる？何がもっとかっこいいか？
Say, do you guys know what's even cooler?
ステージがかっこいいかん？
Like, the stage is cool, right?
きら、いつかまたみんながこぼアイドルって...
Killa, when will you guys see Kobo as an idol...
うわぁーーっ！
Waaaaah!
え、カメラ、カメラ！ちょっと待ってって！
Eh, camera, camera! Wait a second!
ちょっと待ってって！あーい！
Wait a second! Aiy!
こぼが今、
Kobo, right now...
3D配信なのよ！
This is a 3D stream!
いや東海が見えたから遊びに来たんだよ今日。
Well, we saw Tokai so we came to visit today.
な、なんで？ここ？
W-Why? Here?
フライ！
Fly!
フライフライフライ、シッティング、シッティング！
Fly fly fly, sitting, sitting!
ダメだよ！こぼがステージ！ダメだよ！
No way! Kobo's stage! No way!
ほうせい！ほうせい！ほうせい！
Housei! Housei! Housei!
おいおいおいおいおい！
Hey hey hey hey hey!
え、ゆ、ゆくす、フライ？
Eh, Yu, Yux, fly?
あ、せ、せっフライ？せ、せっせっせっせっ
Ah, se, se-fly? Se-se-se-se-se
や、まあ、彼らもうここにいるから、えっと、私たちも何かしようか。
Well, since they're already here, um, let's do something together.
We wanna take the stage for spin, spin!
Spin spin, ok! Ok! Spin spin spin spin spin!
ああ痛い痛い！違うよ！
Ow ow ow! That's wrong!
違うよ！スピンじゃない！
That's wrong! It's not spin!
ノースピン？ノースピン？
No spin? No spin?
えいと、あー、なん、えー、perform together ok? Perform?
Eight, ah, wha, eh, perform together ok? Perform?
お、perform? Ok ok ok!
Oh, perform? Ok ok ok!
あ、first、sit down please ok?
Ah, first, sit down please ok?
Sit down, sit down, sit down, sit down!
あ、sit down, sit down! これ、これ！
Ah, sit down, sit down! This, this!
これがこぼの配信！Sit down, sit down! これは私の配信のよ！
This is Kobo's stream! Sit down, sit down! This is my stream!
Ok! Sit down!
I have something to put on your head!
Okay, ちょっと待ってね、ちょっと待ってね！
Okay, wait a minute, wait a minute!
お、なんだ？なんだ？えっ？
Oh, what? What? Eh?
えっ？えっ？うわあー！
Eh? Eh? Waaaah!
頭が...リアリア、リアリア、セリ、カモンカモンリアリア！
My head is... Riria, riria, seri, come on come on riria riria!
リアリアリアリアリア...あがれ！リアリアノー！
Riria riria riria riria... rise! Riria no!
動きな、動きな！うわあー！
Don't move, don't move! Waaaah!
Ok ok! うまうまうまうま...うわあー！
Ok ok! Uma uma uma uma... Waaaah!
あ、やあやあカモンカモンカモンカモン！Ok!
Ah, yayayay come on come on come on come on! Ok!
痛い痛い痛い痛い！うわあー！はい！
Ow ow ow ow! Waaaah! Hai!
はい！おいしい！
Hai! Delicious!
カモンカモン！お,あ,あ,痛い痛い痛い痛い！
Come on come on! Oh, ah, ah, ow ow ow ow!
無理無理！いてててて！
No way! Ouch ouch ouch ouch!
いった！Ok! マイっかそう！
Ouch! Ok! Guess it's fine!
あい！うわあ、すごい！
Ai! Woah, amazing!
これ、これ、これ何？新しい girl group だよ！
This, this, this what? It's a new girl group!
Girl group!
はいはいはいはい！もう、ok ok!
Hai hai hai hai! Already, ok ok!
Ok, let's go! ポジし、ポジし、ポジション、ok?
Ok, let's go! Posi-si, posi-si, position, ok?
Ok ok! はい！
Ok ok! Hai!
あなたのアイドール
The one and only idol for you
サインはB (chu!)
And the sign is B! (Chu!)
B小町！フーフー！
B-Komachi! Fu-fuu!
ようやく会えたね 嬉しいね 待ち遠しくて足をバタバタさせながら
Finally got to meet you, so happy I flew, dancing with excitement while waiting
今日楽しみで寝れなかったよ
I couldn't sleep because I was looking forward to today
あれも！
That too!
じっとレイクしてる場合じゃない 1分1秒無駄になんてできない
There's no time to just sit around, we can't waste a single second
さあ始めましょう 君も君も君も
Now let's begin, you too, you too, you too!
ア・ナ・タのアイドル サインはB♡
The one and only idol for you, and the sign is B!
ようやく会えたね 嬉しいね
Such joy to meet on this very day!
待ち遠しくて 足をバタバタしながら
My legs are restless, can't contain my nervous sway
今日楽しみで寝られなかったよ
I couldn't sleep well, excitement took its hold
緊張なんかしてる場合じゃない
Now's not the time for nervousness or fear
1分1秒無駄になってできない
Don't waste a moment, let's start, my dear!
さあ始めましょう
Yes, let's play the music
君も！君も！君も！
You too, you too, you too!
お待たせどうさま
We've awaited this day!
手を鳴らせ いらっしゃいませ
Raise your hands, welcome, one and all!
「好き」が集まる場所へようこそ
To the place where love will gather, hear its call!
日常はクロークの中
Normal life may be dark, a little gray
ここに来たならば踊らにゃ損！損！損！
But when you come here, dance, dance, dance!
客席が居ようが居まいが関係ない
I don't care if people watch or not
会場がが大きい小さいとか気にしない
I don't mind if the box is big or small
ちゃんと見えてる君のサイリウム
Clearly, through your reality, I can see
今はフーッと吹けば飛ぶような
Now I feel like I'm about to fly
小さな小さな才能だけど
Singing and dancing, my talent reaching the sky
私を推してくれるのなら爆レスをあげる
Come here, support me, and I'll give my all
ア・ナ・タのアイドル サインはB♡
The one and only idol for you, and the sign is B!
ありがとう！ありがとう！ありがとう！
Thank you! Thank you! Thank you!
じゃあバイバイ！バイバイ！バイバイ！
Well then, bye-bye! Bye-bye! Bye-bye!
ゴーゴーゴーゴー ゴーウェイ！
Go go go go go away!
ネクストネクスト ネクストネクスト！
Next, next, next, next!
バイバイ！バイバイ！バイバイ！
Bye-bye! Bye-bye! Bye-bye!
皆さんお疲れ様でした！
Good work, everyone!
いやーめっちゃ踊り疲れたけどさー、疲れた！
Man, I'm so tired from dancing... so tired!
Ya, tidak terasa sudah di penghujung acara ya kita.
Yeah, we're already reaching the end of the stream, huh?
Ya, barangkali ada yang tertarik ya agensi-agensi modeling, pemancingan, persawahan.
Yeah, maybe some modeling agencies, fishing spots, or rice fields are interested.
Ya, aku mau nunjukin sesuatu, oke?
Yeah, I wanna show you guys something, okay?
Yaitu eh... Tadan!
Which is, uh... Tada!
Kartu nama aku ya! Jadi, bisa banget ya Bapak, Ibu, jika tertarik bisa hubungi saya lewat sini ya.
My business card! So, if you're interested, you can contact me right through here.
Oke nih, silakan. Hm... Apa?
Okay, please. Hm... What?
Ah ini, apa Kobo? Ini apa? Oh iya.
Ah, what is this, Kobo? What is this? Oh yeah.
Ini itu adalah card case! Ini card case. Jadi tuh... Kobo nyimpen kartu nama tuh di card case itu.
This is a card case! This is a card case. So... Kobo stores her business cards in this card case.
Ya, oh kalian mau juga? Soalnya keren banget! Ah, sumpil!
Yeah, oh you guys want one too? Cuz it's so cool! Seriously!
Ya, keren banget ya tuh tuh tuh. Ya udah ya udah, sikat enggak naik.
Yeah, it's so cool, look, look, look. Alright alright, let's grab it.
Tapi Kobo cuma punya satu doang. Hmmm... Tapi it's okay, it's okay, karena kalian bisa purchase it online, oke?
But Kobo only has one. Hmmm... But it's okay, because you guys can purchase it online, okay?
Oke, oke. Jadi semua bisa kedapatan. Hehehe. Ya udah, dibeli ya, ini keren banget bisa buat melindungi kartu KTP, kartu pelajar, kartu SIM, kartu STNK...
Okay, okay. So everyone can get one. Hehehe. So yeah, buy it, it's great for protecting your ID, student card, license...
Semua kartu lah, pokoknya bisalah. Oke? Oke, mantap.
All kinds of cards, basically anything. Okay? Okay, awesome.
Lalu next, aku mau menginformasikan besok, tomorrow! hololive Indonesia 3rd generation h3ro Night Live!
And next, I want to announce that tomorrow, tomorrow! hololive Indonesia 3rd generation h3ro Night Live!
Lucu kan, gila keren banget. Oke, note down the date, alright? Note down the date, oke? Kalian catat, oke? Oke, nice, nice.
Isn't it cute? Man, it's so cool. Okay, note down the date, alright? Note down the date, okay? You guys take note, okay? Okay, nice, nice.
Oke, last but not least, aku masih ada pengumuman penting lainnya nih. Apa ya? Apa ya?
Okay, last but not least, I still have another important announcement. What could it be? What could it be?
Ya udah yuk, lihat bareng-bareng aja videonya.
Let's just watch the video together.
Kobo Kanaeru / 2023.12
[Kobo Kanaeru / December 2023]
NEW SONG RELEASE!!
お楽しみに！Stay Tuned! Nantikan Eaak!!
Stay Tuned!
啊pa! 啊pa! Universal! Itu apa maksudnya Kobo?
Huh?! Universal! What does that mean, Kobo?
Aduh, aku juga enggak tahu. Ya, I don't know what is that. Just be patience, okay? Coming soon really really soon, okay?
Oh, I don't know either. Yeah, I don't know what it is. Just be patient, okay? Coming soon really, really soon, okay?
Ya, ya udah, terima kasih ya guys. Kalau gitu, terakhir deh aku nunjukin gigi aku.
Yeah, alright, thank you guys. If so, last one, I'll show you my teeth.
Aaa... Susah susah susah. Ya udah kalau gitu, dadah guys, bye-bye.
Ahh... Hard, hard, hard. Well then, bye-bye guys, bye-bye.
Kobo harus meninggalkan kalian sekarang. Bye-bye. Dadah semuanya.
Kobo has to leave you guys now. Bye-bye. Bye-bye, everyone.
Thank you everybody for being here tonight!
Yo! Mantra Hujan!
Bapak-bapak, ibu-ibu, adik-adik, siapapun di segala usia...
Gentlemen, ladies, kids, everyone of all ages...
Let's sing it together!
Mina, ikuzo!
Everyone, let's go!
Rappalkan mantra, kilau cahaya, sinari dunia
Recite the mantra, glowing light, illuminating the world...
Sunyi dan sepi di ruang hampa
Silence and loneliness in the empty space...
Masalah datang dan pergi sudah biasa
Problems coming and going is nothing new...
Sendiri lagi, enggan untuk melangkah
Alone again, reluctant to take a step...
Kubuka mata, menatap langit, rintik hujan bergema
I open my eyes, gazing at the sky, raindrops echo...
Genangi ben tala, seakan membisik, \"Ayo jelajahi dunia\"
Flooding my thoughts, as if whispering, "Let's explore the world!"
Melamunkan berbagai angan
Daydreaming of various hopes...
Tak akan selesaikan masalah
Won't solve your problems.
Beranikan diri untuk melangkah
Daring yourself to take a step...
Terobos segala rintangan
Breaking through every obstacle!
Walau hujan tak kunjung berhenti
Even if the rain doesn't stop,
Masih ada aku temani mu di sini
I'm still here to accompany you.
Rappalkan mantra datangkan cahaya
Recite the mantra, bring forth the light...
'Tuk sinari hari-harimu
To brighten your days!
Hilangkan semua rasa ragu yang selimuti hati pikiran dan emosi
Banish all doubts that shroud the heart, mind, and emotions...
Rappalkan mantra datangkan cahaya, buka lembaran yang baru
Recite the mantra, bring forth the light, open a new page!
Ah, susah tidur ku semalaman
Ah, couldn't sleep all night...
Deg-depan hati sampai meriang
Heart racing with feverish excitement!
Tak sabar 'tuk bersenang-senang
Can't wait to have fun...
Di panggung megah bersama kalian
On this grand stage together with you all!
Kau yang sedih di sini di sana
You who are sad here and there...
Your happy sunrise memberi kehangatan
Your happy sunrise brings warmth...
Merebut hati para pedamba
Stealing the hearts of the yearning ones...
Ku lukis indahnya senyuman
I paint a beautiful smile.
Melamunkan berbagai angan
Daydreaming of various hopes...
Tak akan selesaikan masalah
Won't solve your problems.
Beranikan diri untuk melangkah
Daring yourself to take a step...
Terobos segala rintangan
Breaking through every obstacle!
Walau hujan tak kunjung berhenti
Even if the rain doesn't stop,
Masih ada aku temani mu di sini
I'm still here to accompany you.
Rappalkan mantra datangkan cahaya
Recite the mantra, bring forth the light...
'Tuk sinari hari-harimu
To brighten your days!
Hilangkan semua rasa ragu yang selimuti hati pikiran dan emosi
Banish all doubts that shroud the heart, mind, and emotions...
Rappalkan mantra datangkan cahaya, buka lembaran yang baru
Recite the mantra, bring forth the light, open a new page!
Rappalkan mantra datangkan cahaya
Recite the mantra, bring forth the light...
'Tuk sinari hari-harimu
To brighten your days!
Hilangkan semua rasa ragu yang selimuti hati pikiran dan emosi
Banish all doubts that shroud the heart, mind, and emotions...
Rappalkan mantra datangkan cahaya, buka lembaran yang baru
Recite the mantra, bring forth the light, open a new page!
Party people! Get ready!
Kudutch thumbs up in the air!
Put your thumbs up in the air!
Hilangkan semua rasa ragu yang selimuti hati pikiran dan emosi
Banish all doubts that shroud the heart, mind, and emotions...
Rappalkan mantra datangkan cahaya, buka lembaran yang baru
Recite the mantra, bring forth the light, open a new page!
Boko bokobo kobo, Kobo Kanaeru at your service!
Let me be your sun to shine your day!
Congratulations Kobo, congratulations!
Kau mau aku hug?
Do you want me to hug you?
Kawaii, kawaii!
Weeeh! Weeeh! Weeeh! Weeeh!
Woah! Woah! Woah! Woah!
Oh my god!
Pegang tangan Yagoo.
Hold Yagoo's hand.
Ayo, ayo, oke, oke.
Come on, come on, okay, okay.
Ayo Yagoo, ayo Yagoo, let's go.
Come on Yagoo, come on Yagoo, let's go.
Yagoo-san, Yagoo-san. Kunci, kunci.
Yagoo-san, Yagoo-san. Lock it, lock it.
Halo Boss, jangan malu-malu sini napapa, eh.
Hello Boss, don't be shy, come here, it's fine.
Woe!
Whoa!
Now he's covering us! No!
Yeah!
You still grow up, Yagoo-san! Let's go, let's go!
You're still young, Yagoo-san! Let's go, let's go!
No, just kidding.
Hadeh, selesai. Hai shin!
Phew, done. Hi shin!
Wota!
Bye-bye Yagoo. Bye-bye Yagoo. Terima kasih Yagoo.
Bye-bye Yagoo. Bye-bye Yagoo. Thank you, Yagoo.
Bye-bye Daddy. Thank you, thank you!
Yagoo-san, Yagoo-san. Coba tunggu.
Yagoo-san, Yagoo-san. Wait a second.
Sungkem, sungkem dulu.
Bow down, bow down first.
Ah, oke, oke, oke!
Ah, okay, okay, okay!
Oh my god! Biar sopan, biar sopan.
Oh my god! To be polite, to be polite.
Yagoo will love you. Arigato Yagoo.
I trust you. Thank you Yagoo.
Let's get the nail, Yagoo-san! Bye-bye! Peace yo!
Come with me, come with me, bye-bye!
Oke, take care Yagoo-san.
Okay, take care, Yagoo-san.
Semua, terima kasih sudah nonton!
Everyone, thank you for watching!
Terima kasih sudah nonton, terima kasih!
Thank you for watching, thank you!
Bye-bye! Mwaaah!